HEY.
WOW. YOU LOOK NICE;
WHAT'S THE OCCASION?
MONICA AND I ARE CELEBRATING
OUR TEN-MONTH ANNIVERSARY.
GOT RESERVATIONS
AT JEAN-GEORGES.
WELL... HOW'D YOU
GET IN THERE?
AH, MADE A FEW CALLS,
PULLED SOME STRINGS
AND THEY AGREED
TO SEAT US AT 11:30
IF WE BOTH HAD THE CHICKEN
AND DIDN'T GET DESSERT.
I SEE.
( knocking )
HI, CHANDLER.
HEY, CAITLIN.
SOMEBODY GOT A HAIRCUT.
UGH. I HATE IT.
I LOOK LIKE AN
EIGHT-YEAR-OLD BOY.
YEAH, WELL, IF THAT WAS TRUE,
GYM CLASS WOULD HAVE BEEN
A LOT MORE INTERESTING.
( chuckles )
IT'S, UH, $27 EVEN.
OH, OKAY. THERE YOU GO.
( duck quacking )
HEY, WHERE'S THE CHICKEN?
OH, HE'S IN THE BACK.
THE DUCK PISSED HIM OFF--
SAID THAT EGGS CAME FIRST.
THANKS. I'LL
SEE YOU LATER.
OKAY, BYE.
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
WHAT?
THE FLIRTING.
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO BE GOING
OUT WITH-- UH, I DON'T KNOW--
HMM, LET'S SEE--
MY SISTER?!
I WAS NOT FLIRTING.
IT WAS TOTALLY FLIRTING.
"SOMEBODY GOT A HAIRCUT."
( talking gibberish )
OKAY, FIRST OF ALL,
THE IMPRESSION? UNCANNY.
AND SECOND, THAT WAS
NOT FLIRTING. THAT WAS
JUST CASUAL CONVERSATION
BETWEEN TWO PEOPLE;
THAT IS ALL.
YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU WANT TO SEE FLIRTING?
I'LL SHOW YOU FLIRTING.
I'M GOOD. I'M GOOD.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
I AM SO PROUD OF JOEY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S GOING
TO BE ON LAW AND ORDER.
I KNOW, BUT
DON'T YOU THINK
THAT IT SHOULD BE
CALLED "ORDER AND LAW"?
NO, BECAUSE FIRST THEY ARREST
THE GUY, AND THEN THEY TRY HIM.
YEAH, DON'T GET ME
STARTED ON THAT.
I WAS NOT FLIRTING.
AND ON YOUR ANNIVERSARY--
FOR SHAME.
Rachel:
WHAT'S GOING ON?
CHANDLER WAS HITTING
ON THE HOT DELIVERY GIRL.
I WAS NOT AND,
OH, GOD, SHH!
WELL, I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU WERE, OKAY?
AND BESIDES, IF ANYONE
SHOULD BE HITTING ON HER
IT'S THE GUY
WHO'S SINGLE, OKAY?
THE GUY WHO CAN DO
SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
SOUNDS LIKE SOMEONE WANTS
TO BE MR. PIZZA DELIVERY GIRL.
WELL...
IS THAT WHAT
THIS IS ABOUT?
YOU LIKE CAITLIN?
( chuckling ):
ROSS, WE BROKE UP
TWO YEARS AGO.
YOU'VE BEEN MARRIED
SINCE THEN.
I THINK IT'S OKAY THAT
WE SEE OTHER PEOPLE.
WELL, I WAS WATCHING HER
THE OTHER DAY
AT THE PIZZA PLACE,
AND SHE WAS JUST SO SEXY
AND FUNNY AND HAS
THE CUTEST LITTLE...
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE DON'T NEED HER MEASUREMENTS.
OKAY, PEPPERONI,
PEPPERONI, PEPPERONI.
ROSS, I KNOW SHE'S PRETTY
AND YOU LOVE HER
BUT IS SHE STUPID?
SHE FORGOT MY VEGETARIAN.
THIS IS PERFECT.
SHE'LL HAVE TO COME BACK HERE
WITH YOUR PIZZA
AND, WHEN SHE DOES, I WILL TURN
ON THE CHARM-O'-ROSS.
OH, I AM SO GLAD
YOU DON'T EAT MEAT.
SEE? VEGETARIANISM
BENEFITS EVERYONE.
HEY, EVERYBODY,
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
YOU REMEMBER
MY GRANDMOTHER?
All: HI!
BUONA SERA.
BIG NIGHT.
YEAH, IT'S SO COOL.
SO, JOEY ON LAW AND ORDER--
YOU MUST BE VERY PROUD.
CHANDLER, SHE DOESN'T
UNDERSTAND A WORD OF ENGLISH.
I'M SORRY. I THOUGHT YOU WERE
JOEY'S OTHER GRANDMOTHER.
I'VE DONE IT AGAIN.
NO, NONNI--
NONNI'S MY BIGGEST FAN.
YEAH, SHE'S THE ONLY ONE
IN THE FAMILY
WHO'S ALWAYS BELIEVED IN ME.
SI, NONNI?
IO SONO NUMERO UNO, NO?
( Italian accent ):
SI, BIG STAR.
MY BIG FAT JOEY STAR.
( chuckles )
YEAH, I WEIGHED, LIKE, 27 POUNDS
WHEN I WAS BORN.
HEY, HAPPY ANNIVERSARY.
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY,
TEN MONTHS.
OH...
SO, UM, WHEN I
WAS IN THE SHOWER
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
OUR FIRST NIGHT IN LONDON.
OH, JOEY'S GRANDMOTHER'S
RIGHT THERE.
IS THAT THE ONE WHO
SPEAKS ENGLISH OR
THE ONE WHO DOESN'T?
THE ONE WHO DOESN'T.
THAT WAS SOME HOT LOVE
YOU GAVE ME.
I'M GOING TO GO GET READY.
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU WEAR
THOSE EARRINGS I GOT YOU?
OH, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
I WAS SAVING THEM
FOR SOMETHING SPECIAL.
OKAY.
YOU'VE GOT TO GO HOME.
BUT I LIKE IT HERE.
YOU GOT TO GO HOME
AND GET THE EARRINGS THAT
YOU BORROWED FROM ME, OKAY?
CHANDLER WANTS ME
TO WEAR THEM TONIGHT.
OKAY. I THINK
THEY'RE IN MY PURSE.
WHY DON'T YOU GO GET DRESSED?
AND I'LL LOOK FOR THEM.
GREAT.
OKAY.
RACH, HI.
I NEED THOSE EARRINGS
YOU BORROWED.
OH, UM... OKAY.
YEAH. I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OKAY.
SCUSA, SIGNORA.
( speaking Italian )
NIENTE, GRAZIE.
( speaks Italian )
( giggles )
WOW, PHEEBS,
YOU SPEAK ITALIAN?
I GUESS SO.
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
WAIT, RACH.
WHERE'S THE OTHER ONE?
OH, WHAT?
YOU WANT BOTH OF THEM?
RACHEL KAREN GREEN,
WHERE IS THE OTHER EARRING?
OKAY, OKAY. OKAY, LOOK,
JUST DON'T FREAK OUT
BUT I KIND OF LOST IT.
I KNOW IT'S
IN THE APARTMENT
BUT I DEFINITELY LOST IT.
WHAT AM I GOING TO TELL MONICA?
SHE WANTS TO WEAR THEM TONIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW. TELL HER
TO WEAR HER OWN EARRINGS.
THESE ARE
HER EARRINGS.
NO, NO!
YOU LENT ME
MONICA'S EARRINGS?!
I'M NOT ALLOWED
TO BORROW HER STUFF!
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE I LOSE HER STUFF!
He left a little
after 2:00.
OKAY, NOW, YOU SEE
THAT BLIND GUY RIGHT THERE?
I'M GOING TO BASH
HIS HEAD IN LATER.
DOV'E, JOEY?
MY BIG SCENE'S COMING UP.
THE BIG SCENE COMING UP.
IF YOU SAID,
"BIG LIMA BEAN BUBBLING UP"
WOULD SHE UNDERSTAND
THE DIFFERENCE?
RACH, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
OH, I-I JUST CAN'T WATCH.
IT'S TOO SCARY.
IT'S A DIAPER
COMMERCIAL.
OH, YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW ME
AND BABIES... RESPONSIBILITIES.
( mock scream )
( knock at door )
Caitlin:
PIZZA DELIVERY!
I'LL GET IT!
I WILL GET THAT!
HI.
ONE VEGETARIAN PIZZA.
IT'S $12.15.
OH. UH, BY THE WAY
IF IT MAKES YOU
FEEL ANY BETTER
I HAPPEN TO LIKE
EIGHT-YEAR-OLD BOYS.
WHAT?
( stuttering ):
NO... OH, I MEAN...
THE, UH... YOUR
HAIR... BEFORE...
YOUR HAIR... YOU
SAID YOU THOUGHT
THAT YOUR HAIR LOOKED LIKE
AN EIGHT-YEAR-OLD BOY'S
AND I'M, I'M JUST
SAYING, I LIKE IT--
THE-THE HAIR.
OH. THANKS.
YOU UNDERSTAND I DON'T ACTUALLY
LIKE EIGHT-YEAR-OLD BOYS.
YOU KNOW, ALL I'M
LOOKING FOR IS THE MONEY.
HERE YOU GO. NOW, STOP
BRINGING US PIZZAS, YOU.
I'M GOING TO TRY.
BYE.
( sighs )
YOU'RE WELCOME.
YOU COULDN'T LET ME
HAVE HER, COULD YOU?
WHAT?
THIS IS A GIRL
I REALLY LIKE
AND YOU, YOU HAD
TO SWOOP IN THERE!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
CHANDLER WAS TOTALLY FLIRTING
WITH THE HOT DELIVERY GIRL.
THANK YOU FOR THAT.
I WAS NOT FLIRTING.
IT'S OKAY. I DON'T CARE.
IT'S FINE.
REALLY?
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I DO IT ALL THE TIME.
( chuckles )
SO, UH...
( clears throat )
YOU-YOU-YOU FLIRT
WITH GUYS ALL THE TIME?
SURE. IT DOESN'T
MEAN ANYTHING.
JUST LIKE I KNOW
IT DOESN'T MEAN
ANYTHING WITH YOU.
OKAY, BUT THERE'S
A BIG DIFFERENCE, ALL RIGHT?
YOU ARE A LOT HOTTER
THAN I AM.
TRUE STORY.
CHANDLER, THIS
ACTUALLY BOTHERS YOU?
YES, IT DOES BOTHER ME.
I THINK IT'D BOTHER
A LOT OF PEOPLE.
RACHEL, WHEN YOU WERE
GOING OUT WITH ROSS
DID IT BOTHER YOU
WHEN HE FLIRTED
WITH OTHER WOMEN?
UH, NO. NO,
IT BOTHERED ME
WHEN HE SLEPT
WITH OTHER WOMEN.
AND THANK YOU FOR THAT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I NEVER REALLY
HAD ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
ROSS WAS NEVER VERY GOOD
AT THE FLIRTING THING.
WHA-WHA...?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
IT WORKED WITH YOU.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE MET, YOU FLIRTED
AND THEN BAM!
NINE YEARS LATER,
YOU HAD ME.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO?
I AM GOING TO ORDER
ANOTHER PIZZA
AND WHEN CAITLIN GETS HERE
YOU-- I WILL SHOW YOU
HOW WELL I FLIRT.
IN FACT, I WILL--
I WILL GET
HER PHONE NUMBER--
WELL...
AND NOT THE ONE
ON THE MENU.
I FOUND IT.
( gasps ):
OH, THANK GOD!
WHERE WAS IT?
ON YOUR DRESSER.
OKAY, THAT IS THE ONE
WE ALREADY HAVE.
OH!
OKAY, HERE'S
MY BIG SCENE.
MY BIG SCENE'S HERE.
What do you bet,
nobody heard anything?
No bet.
Anybody home?
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT?
OKAY, EVERYBODY
JUST KEEP SMILING.
IT'LL KILL MY GRANDMOTHER
IF SHE FINDS OUT.
WHAT IS IT?
THEY CUT ME OUT
OF THE SHOW.
WHAT?
ARE YOU SURE?
MAYBE YOUR SCENE'S
COMING UP.
NOT LIKELY, 'CAUSE YOU SEE
THAT BODY BAG RIGHT THERE?
YEAH.
I'M IN IT.
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW. THIS LITTLE
OLD LADY LIVES FOR MY CAREER.
WHEN THEY DUMPED ME OFF DAYS
OF OUR LIVES, SHE ALMOST DIED.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
YOU'RE NOT SMILING.
NOT THAT FACE.
SMILE. EVERYBODY SMILE!
JOEY, WHY DON'T YOU
JUST TELL HER WHAT HAPPENED?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
IF WE KEEP TALKING THIS WAY,
AREN'T WE GOING
TO FREAK HER OUT SOON?
( speaking Italian )
OH, UH, UH, SOON. SOON.
I'M GOING TO BE ON SOON.
I... THERE I AM!
I'll let you know.
Grandma:
NO!
SAM WATERSTON.
NO, NO, NO. THAT'S...
THAT'S ME. THAT'S ME.
NO. SAM WATERSTON.
CRIME MISDEMEANOR,
CAPRICORN ONE...
SHE DOESN'T KNOW "HELLO,"
BUT SHE KNOWS CAPRICORN ONE.
PHOEBE?
HMM?
I HAVE TO HAVE
THOSE EARRINGS.
WE'RE GOING TO LEAVE
AS SOON AS THE SHOW'S OVER.
BUT I ALREADY
GAVE THEM BACK TO YOU.
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
ALL RIGHT, I ALREADY
DIDN'T GAVE THEM BACK TO YOU.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
RACHEL, WHERE IS
THAT OTHER EARRING?
IT'S NOT HERE, PHEEBS.
IT'S NOT HERE.
OH! I WENT TO JOEY
AND CHANDLER'S LAST NIGHT.
OKAY. MAKE SURE YOU CHECK
CHANDLER'S JEWELRY BOX.
WAIT A MINUTE. WHAT?
CHANDLER HAS A JEWELRY BOX?
OKAY, WE HAVE,
LIKE, TEN MINUTES.
DO YOU WANT ME
TO GET INTO THAT NOW?
HEY, PHEEBS.
HOW'S THAT, UH...
VEGETARIAN PIZZA
WORKING OUT FOR YOU, HUH?
YOU AND
THOSE VEGETABLES
HAVE A REAL THING
GOING ON, HUH?
WHY ARE YOU BEING WEIRD?
DO YOU LIKE IT?
NO. THAT WOULD BE,
"WHY ARE YOU BEING CUTE?"
OKAY, I'M WORKING
ON MY FLIRTING.
OH! I DID NOT GET THAT.
SO, MONICA, DO YOU...
DO YOU LIKE THE LAW & ORDER?
YEAH. IT'S GOOD.
SEE, I'M FINDING OUT
ALL THIS STUFF ABOUT YOU TODAY--
LIKE YOU LIKE
THE LAW & ORDER
AND-AND YOU FLIRTED
WITH EVERY GUY IN
THE TRISTATE AREA.
SHH! SHH!
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, LET ME
GET THIS STRAIGHT.
IT'S OKAY FOR YOU TO FLIRT,
BUT NOT FOR ME.
OH, I'M SO GLAD
WE CLEARED THAT UP.
LOOK, I'M SORRY, BUT
SOME THINGS ARE DIFFERENT
FOR MEN AND FOR WOMEN.
GO ON, TEACH ME SOMETHING
ABOUT MEN AND WOMEN.
OKAY, I'VE ALREADY
TAUGHT YOU SO MUCH ALREADY,
BUT WHATEVER...
SEE, WHEN YOU
FLIRT WITH A GUY
YOU THINK, "I'M JUST
FLIRTING. NO BIG DEAL."
BUT THE GUY
IS THINKING "FINALLY,
SOMEBODY WHO WANTS
TO SLEEP WITH ME."
NO WAY!
IT'S TRUE.
THAT'S PATHETIC.
AGAIN, TRUE.
( scoffs )
AND THIS GOES
FOR ALL GUYS?
ALL GUYS THAT ARE AWAKE.
THEN WE GO TO SLEEP.
AND ALL GUYS FROM
THE OTHER END OF THE WORLD
WAKE UP AND BEHAVE
THE EXACT SAME WAY.
ALL RIGHT, IT'S
ANOTHER COMMERCIAL
AND I STILL
HAVEN'T TOLD HER.
JOEY, THIS IS, LIKE,
THE LAST COMMERCIAL.
YOU GOT, LIKE,
TEN MINUTES LEFT.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO? OH!
NO, YOU ARE NOT
GOING TO RUN OUT
AND LEAVE HER HERE.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
OH!
JOEY?
UH... JOEY'S GOING
TO BE RIGHT BACK.
RIGHT... BACK.
( chuckles )
MEANWHILE, LET'S, LET'S,
LET'S TALK ABOUT YOU.
SO... YOU'RE OLD AND SMALL.
DID YOU FIND IT?
THE EARRING? NO.
BUT, LOOK--
I FOUND MY SUNGLASSES
UNDER THE COUCH.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR THESE
SINCE, LIKE, LAST SUMMER.
OKAY, THOSE ARE
MY SUNGLASSES.
YOU BORROWED
THEM FROM ME.
OKAY. CALM DOWN.
HERE THEY ARE.
PHOEBE?
WHAT DO I DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
ALL RIGHT. WELL...
WE'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE
TO TELL MONICA, THAT'S ALL.
OH, GOD, SHE'S
GOING TO KILL ME.
I SUPPOSE I COULD TELL HER
IT WAS JUST ALL MY FAULT.
OH, THAT
WOULD BE GREAT.
MON, CAN I TALK
TO YOU FOR A SEC?
YEAH. WHAT IS IT?
UM... I LOST ONE
OF YOUR EARRINGS.
I'M SORRY.
I AM SO, SO SORRY.
WOW...
ALL RIGHT. WELL, I MEAN...
WHAT CAN YOU DO?
IF YOU LOST IT, YOU LOST IT.
I'LL REPLACE IT, I PROMISE.
I FEEL SO TERRIBLE.
ALL RIGHT, SWEETIE, THAT'S FINE.
YOU DIDN'T DO IT ON PURPOSE.
NO.
LOOK AT YOU.
COME HERE.
AW...
IS THAT BETTER?
YEAH. YOU'RE THE BEST.
OKAY, WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT A MINUTE. I-I-I...
I CAN'T DO THIS.
LISTEN, HONEY, THIS IS...
IT'S NOT PHOEBE'S FAULT.
SHE LENT ME
THE EARRINGS.
I LOST IT.
I'M SO SORRY, HONEY.
I FEEL TERRIBLE, TOO.
THAT IS EXACTLY
WHY I DO NOT
LEND YOU STUFF!
OKAY?
FIRST, IT'S MY JEWELRY!
IF IT'S NOT MY JEWELRY,
IT'S MY BLUE SWEATER!
IF IT'S NOT
MY BLUE SWEATER,
IT'S MY SUNGLASSES!
YOUR SUNGLASSES?
YES!
OH, RIGHT.
( knocking on door )
PIZZA!
MINE! MINE! MINE!
OKAY, HERE GOES.
PREPARE YOURSELVES
FOR SOME CLASS "A" FLIRTING.
OKAY, HOLD ON.
OKAY.
HEY, YOU HAVE
NOTHING TO PROVE.
AND IF YOU REALLY LIKE THIS GIRL
I DON'T THINK FLIRTING'S
THE RIGHT WAY TO...
UH! UH! UH! UH! UH!
YOU'LL SEE. OKAY.
WH-WHAT'S HER NAME?
All:
CAITLIN.
( giggling )
HEY!
OH, WE... WE CAN'T
KEEP EATING LIKE THIS.
IT'S, UH.... $12.50.
OKAY. UM...
SO...
DO YOU...
MAKE THE PIZZAS
IN ONE OF THOSE, UH...
WOOD-BURNING OVENS?
NO. ACTUALLY, UM...
I THINK THEY'RE GAS.
GAS? WOW!
INTENSE.
IF THIS IS THE WAY
ALL THE GELLERS FLIRT
WE DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM.
HEY, UH... YOU KNOW
THAT SMELL GAS HAS?
YEAH.
THEY PUT THAT IN.
WHAT?
THE GAS IS ODORLESS
BUT THEY ADD THE SMELL
SO YOU KNOW
WHEN THERE'S A LEAK.
WELL, OKAY.
A LOT OF
OTHER GAS SMELLS.
OH, THE HUMANITY.
ME-METHANE SMELLS.
YOU KNOW WHAT? UM...
ACTUALLY, I...
I REALLY... I SHOULD GO.
OH, BUT I-I... I
HAVEN'T PAID YOU YET.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S OKAY.
YOU GUYS HAVE ORDERED SO MANY
THAT THIS ONE'S ON ME.
WAS I TALKING TO HER ABOUT GAS?
MORE SO THAN
ANYTHING ELSE.
I-I... I FOUND
IT INTERESTING.
I'M SORRY.
HEY, HEY,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IN NINE YEARS,
SHE AND I WILL BE RIGHT THERE.
OKAY, WELL, I'M GOING TO
CLEAR OUT SOME OF THESE BOXES.
ROSS?
YEAH?
WHAT ELSE DO THEY
ADD SMELL TO?
CAITLIN.
CAITLIN, HI.
HI, HI, HI. I'M RACHEL.
FROM UPSTAIRS? THE PEOPLE
WITH ALL THE PIZZA?
OH, WAS THERE A PROBLEM?
NO, NO, NO.
EVERYTHING,
THEY'RE FINE. GREAT PIZZA.
BUT IT'S ACTUALLY, UM,
MY FRIEND, ROSS.
HE, UH, HE JUST GETS REALLY
NERVOUS WHEN HE'S FLIRTING.
OH, MY GOD.
THAT WAS FLIRTING?
YEAH. I KNOW.
WOW.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
BUT, UH, JUST...
I'M TELLING YOU.
ONCE... ONCE YOU GET
PAST THAT PART
WHERE IT JUST FEELS
LIKE YOU WANT TO DIE
UM, HE'S... HE'S
A REALLY GOOD PERSON.
THE GUY WITH THE GAS?
YEAH. I-I...
I'M TELLING YOU.
HE'S REALLY SWEET
AND HE'S REALLY FUNNY
AND HE'S JUST...
OH, JUST GOT A GOOD HEART.
AND BESIDES, I THINK
HE REALLY LIKES YOU.
REALLY?
YOU KNOW,
WE HAVE SEVEN PEOPLE
AND, LIKE, TEN PIZZAS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I JUST... I THOUGHT
JOEY WAS THERE.
Man:
You have till Monday
then I move to dismiss.
HEY, ROSS?
UM... I JUST RAN
INTO CAITLIN
IN THE HALLWAY
AND-AND, UH... YOU
MUST BE GETTING BETTER
AT THIS FLIRTING STUFF
THAN I THOUGHT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, I DON'T GET IT
BUT SHE WANTED ME
TO GIVE YOU HER PHONE NUMBER.
AND SHE JUST
GAVE YOU THIS?
YEAH.
RACH, THANKS,
BUT I DON'T NEED YOU
DOING ME ANY FAVORS.
I DIDN'T. I DIDN'T.
SHE THOUGHT YOU WERE CUTE.
WELL, THAT
I CAN BELIEVE.
YEAH.
HEY! IS THE SHOW STILL ON?
ALMOST OVER, MAN.
HEY, NONNI.
OH! IS THAT THE POPE?
WHY AM I LOOKING?
OH, NONNI, HERE I AM!
LOOK! THIS IS MY BIG SCENE.
All right, back off!
Now, I got a gun.
I'm not afraid to use it.
OH, JOEY!
THAT'S RIGHT, NONNI.
YOU COULDN'T HAVE AT LEAST
CHANGED YOUR SHIRT?
Now, I want a suitcase
filled with $100,000...
( duck quacking )
Shoo! shoo! shoo!
...filled with $100,000
in small bills.
And if I don't get...
( duck quacking )
Shoo!
And if I don't get it...
I'm going to shoot this duck!
OH, NO!
I'm coming out.
AND SHE'S SUPPOSED
TO BUY THIS?
JOEY, BRAVO!
BRAVO! BELLISSIMO! OH!
Ground Control to Major Tom.
Commencing countdown.
Engines...
on.
THAT'S, UH, SCENES
FROM NEXT WEEK'S SHOW.
NEXT WEEK.
I AM DEFINITELY
GOING TO WATCH THAT.
WHAT ABOUT THESE?
DO THESE LOOK THE SAME?
DEFINITELY.
NOT AS EACH OTHER.
OH. THEN, NO.
HEY, YOU READY?
HI. YEAH.
YOU LOOK AMAZING.
I'M THE LUCKIEST MAN
IN THE WORLD.
OH, YOU'RE ABOUT TO
GET A LITTLE LUCKIER.
LET'S SEE
THE EARRINGS.
OH, RIGHT.
THEY LOOK GREAT.
DOES YOUR BOYFRIEND HAVE
THE BEST TASTE OR WHAT?
MY BOYFRIEND REALLY
DOES HAVE GREAT TASTE.
THANKS FOR PICKING OUT
THE EARRINGS, MAN.
MM-HMM.